greenwood-management.com 2013-12-22

# Privacy Policy

### Greenwood Management Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy covers Greenwood Management and its treatment of information we collect when you are on our site and when you use our services. This policy also covers our treatment of any personally identifiable information our business partners share with us. This policy does not apply to the practices of Greenwood Management agents that it does not own or control, or to individuals Greenwood Management does not employ or manage, including operators of sites to which you may link from the Greenwood Management Web site.

### What information do we gather?

The only personally identifiable information we collect about you is that which you choose to share with us in registration or when responding to offers from Greenwood Management or from our business partners. We also collect information about aggregate site usage. The statistics we gather about unique visits, repeat visits and page views are all based on IP addresses, and are not associated with your personal information.

### Why do we ask for personal information about you?

Our goal at Greenwood Management is to provide you with comprehensive information and community services. The information that we ask you to share with us allows us to improve the site and still keep it free. Aggregate demographic information about our users is valuable to our advertisers, as it provides them with some important, yet anonymous information about potential customers. Without advertising support, we could not keep the site free for your use.

We also collect information so that we can notify you about updates to our Web site, our electronic information products, and our other services.

In the near future, we expect to offer Greenwood Management visitors the ability to customize certain features on our site. This will enable you to return to your personalized version each time you visit the site. To support this personalization, we need to be able to identify your account from session to session. This requires that you provide us with some information about yourself and your company. Your user name, password and e-mail address allow us to differentiate you from other users. They also allow us to contact you about developments and new products on the site.

### How to we use the information we collect?

We may share aggregate site user information with our partners and advertisers at any time. We will not share your personally identifiable information with any third party unless we tell you otherwise when we collect the information. And we will always give you the opportunity to "opt out" of being contacted by Greenwood Management staff. 

When you register at our site and/or "opt in" to receive our free electronic publications, you consent to being contacted by Greenwood Management, its business partners and advertisers. Once you have "opted in" and agreed that your information may be shared with third parties or you have responded to an offer by any third party on the Greenwood Management Web site, Greenwood Management will not be able to update any of your personally identifiable information that has been transferred to such third parties or opt you out of such third parties so that you no longer receive their promotional and/or marketing information. Instead, you must either contact that third party or refer to their privacy policy to update your personal information or to let them know that you no longer want to receive promotional and/or marketing information about their products, services, or offerings.

The bottom line: Sometimes we want personal information from you so that we or our partners and our agents can send you material we think might be of interest to you. We will always tell you up front what we're going to do with your responses, and we will always give you a chance to say "no thanks."

### How does Greenwood Management use cookies?

Greenwood Management uses cookies to speed up the login process for you at various points on the site. When you register with Greenwood Management, we assign a unique user ID to you, and we place a cookie on your computer that will remind our system of that user ID in other areas of the site, or the next time you visit the site. This cookie allows you to access areas of the site without having to log on multiple times. If you choose to log off, this cookie we set in registration will be deleted, and we will then set another cookie like it on your computer next time you log in. 

Please note: Nothing in a cookie allows us to identify you individually. Your computer is assigned a number and that number is tracked using the cookie. This number is only meaningful in the context of our secure database system.

We also use cookies to log your activity on the site. Everything we learn from these logs will be used to enrich your experience on our site. It will help us understand what you like and don't like, so we can focus our energies more effectively and provide you with better information and services.

The only personally identifiable information we collect about you is that which you choose to share with us in registration or when responding to offers from Greenwood Management or from our business partners. As stated earlier, this information will be closely protected and used for internal purposes only, unless we tell you otherwise when we collect the information, you have consented by "opting in" to being contacted by Greenwood Management, its agents, officers, and other associated third parties, or we have informed you of a change to our privacy policy so that you can then choose to opt out. We will never wilfully release your personal information to any third party without providing you notice unless: you direct us to enter you in a contest; you ask us to sign you up for a service that is supported by one of our partners; you otherwise opt in to have your information shared with third parties; we respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; we find your actions on our Web site violate our Terms and Conditions or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services; or we transfer your information in connection with a sale of forestry assets held or promoted through Greenwood Management.

### Changes to the Greenwood Management Privacy Policy

Greenwood Management may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by posting a prominent notice in our privacy policy or in other locations on our Web site or by sending you an email to inform you of our updated privacy policy.

### Spam

We don't like it, we don't support it, and we don't engage in it. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by contacting Customer Service. Be sure to specify whether you want to be removed from a certain e-mail list or all of our product e-mail lists. 

### Customer Service

relations@gwm-tv.com
